[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these lovely singers plays Darrens mother in the 2003 comedy movie The Fighting Temptations?", "correct_answer": "Faith Evans", "incorrect_answers": ["Whitney Houston", "Angie Stone", "Lauryn Hill"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many prestigious industry awards did Popeyes Chicken  Biscuits win at their 30th anniversary?", "correct_answer": "2", "incorrect_answers": ["1", "0", "3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first US Senator to fly on the Space Shuttle?", "correct_answer": "Jake Garn", "incorrect_answers": ["Bill Bradley", "Tom McMillan", "John Glenn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This American car make was founded in 1911, and was purchased by General Motors in 1917.", "correct_answer": "Chevrolet", "incorrect_answers": ["Hummer", "Ford", "Cadillac"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The total assembly of the Boeing 747 would require how many individually numbered and catalogued parts?", "correct_answer": "4 000 000", "incorrect_answers": ["300 000", "5 000 000", "500 000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Putting sugar in the gas tank of a carburetor-equipped vehicle will ruin the engine.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the basic food of the sea. Billions upon billions of these organisms live in the sea.", "correct_answer": "Plankton", "incorrect_answers": ["Seaweed", "Crabs", "Shrimp"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the brownish pigment that gives coloration to the human skin, iris and hair?", "correct_answer": "Melanin", "incorrect_answers": ["Mezamine", "Melamine", "Methylamine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played Clark Kent and Superman in the first Superman movie?", "correct_answer": "Christopher Reeve", "incorrect_answers": ["Brandon Routh", "George Reeves", "Tom Welling"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Early amphibians such as Icthyostega evolved during what geological period?", "correct_answer": "Devonian", "incorrect_answers": ["Silurian", "Carboniferous", "Permian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the story Mikey told in the attic in The Goonies, Willys ship was called the Armada.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many Godzilla movies were produced in Japan from the movie\u2019s debut in 1954 to 2007?", "correct_answer": "28", "incorrect_answers": ["12", "20", "36"]}]